<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ohaiwalt</title>
    <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ohaiwalt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 23:51:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ohaiwalt.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>hello world</title>
      <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 23:51:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think this is probably iteration fourteen of attempting write on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s give this one a go then, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 23:35:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohaiwalt.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Matthew Walter, a site reliability engineer working in NYC. I&amp;rsquo;m working on building a platform to make government beautiful with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.seamlessdocs.com&#34;&gt;SeamlessDocs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After high school, I joined the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.navy.com/&#34;&gt;United States Navy&lt;/a&gt; as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.navy.com/careers/information-and-technology/cryptology.html&#34;&gt;Cryptologic Technician Maintenance&lt;/a&gt; and after a few months in Great Lakes, Illinois and Pensacola, Florida spent three years building communications centers out of Hawaii from 2005-2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As my time wound to a close in Hawaii I changed job fields to &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_systems_technician_(United_States_Navy)&#34;&gt;Information Systems Technician&lt;/a&gt;, and after another few months of training chose orders to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USS_Mount_Whitney_(LCC-20)&#34;&gt;USS Mount Whitney LCC-20&lt;/a&gt; in Gaeta, Italy from 2008-2011. During my time on the Mount Whitney, I was exposed to many manual processes for managing high(er) security environments. After picking up Linux for the first time in 2009, I started to find that there was a better way, and began to focus on learning about automation and software development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After leaving Italy to move to Baltimore, Maryland, I worked as a network engineer doing break/fix on point-to-point SONET lines from 2011-2012. While this was a different learning experience, it left me with 12 hour midnight shifts and nothing to do unless something was broken, so I spent all my available time reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/&#34;&gt;Safari Books&lt;/a&gt; and learning how large scale systems were built and run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I left active duty in September 2012 and moved to Fairfield, Connecticut to attend Fairfield University in pursuit of a B.S in Software Engineering, as I identified that many of my career goals required programming skills. After winter 2013, I left Fairfield University in order to pursue a professional career after an economics professor and I had a long talk about opportunity cost. I continued to maintain an attachment to the Navy Reserve until March of 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>