<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on ohaiwalt</title>
    <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on ohaiwalt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 22:08:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>on committing entirely</title>
      <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/on-committing-entirely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 22:08:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/on-committing-entirely/</guid>
      <description>There was a time in my life where I had trouble committing to things. This time was characterized by dissatisfaction and unhappiness. It didn&amp;rsquo;t really manifest as unhappiness at the time, more it was a low level restlessness that resulted in never sticking with anything, or investing my real and honest self into anything be it relationships, professional development, or hobbies.
After leaving active duty in 2012 and separating from the Navy, I found I missed the water and craved seeing the sunset without land in sight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello world</title>
      <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 23:51:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I think this is probably iteration fourteen of attempting write on a regular basis.
Let&amp;rsquo;s give this one a go then, shall we?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/devember/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohaiwalt.com/blog/devember/</guid>
      <description>A friend introduced me to Devember yesterday, and I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to hop on. Devember is a personal goal of spending an hour a day coding for the month of December, with public accountability.
I&amp;rsquo;ll have a public record on GitHub with some code samples as I create them as well as a daily log of my efforts.
The proclamation:
I, Matthew Walter, will participate to the next Devember. My Devember will be working with Python and Go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>